All rise!
Get seated.
Trial in Seoul District Court begins now.
Case 521, a hit-and-run.
Defendant Kang Yoo Jung, please stand over there.
If you have called an ambulance,
you could've save their lives.
Due to denfendant Kang Yoo Jung's irresponsible act,
a young woman and
her unborn child were dead.
This is inexcusable under any circumstances.
Therefore, we presecutor ask for
a five-year sentence to defendant Kang Yoo Jung.
Number 2008, get in.
Honey.
Move.
Hey, isn't she Ye Ji, the movie star?
She's my target.
Stay away from her.
I'm a big fan of yours.
Can I have your autograph?
Sorry, can I have your autograph, too?
Hey!
So boring.
Honey.
Honey! Where are you?
Do you like playing hide-and-seek?
Miss, go drink with me.
Go away.
Why is he looking at me that way?
Yoo Jung.
Are you available now?
Yes.
Two customers called me just now, wanna take one?
Sure. Thank you. What's the phone number?
It's a male customer, can you handle it?
Sure.
See you later.
I'll be back soon, wait for me!
Hello.
Hey. Hurry up.
This is the address. Go as quickly as possible.
- Thank you. - Be careful.
OK.
Sir, fasten your seatbelt please.
What are you doing?
I'm your designated driver.
Where is the former guy?
I don't know.
What should I do with this? I seemed to press the wrong button.
Leave it alone.
We're off then.
Stop.
What?
Stop the car!
Stop the car! Stop.
Get out of the way.
What are you doing?
Go away.
Sir.
Don't let me say the same thing twice.
Go away or I'll hit you.
How can you be so rude!
That's who I am.
What are you doing?
You're still drunk. You can't drive.
Some people have to earn money while others are asleep.
They can't risk a car accident.
So what?
Give me the key.
Aren't you ashamed?
Call another designated driver or walk home.
Give me the key. Give it to me.
Holy crap.
It seems like you don't want to call another driver,
maybe you should walk home.
Come here.
Kwang Soo!
My phone.
Is that guy crazy?
Why didn't you call Do Hoon?
He is a prosecutor.
No. He doesn't know that I'm a designated driver. I won't tell him.
What an innocent girl.
You can tell from his behaviours.
He must be a sopiled rich guy. Find out where he lives.
If I were you, I won't let him go.
I'll get a large sum of money, or seduce him.
Seduce him?
Don't you just start a new relationship?
Don't be so naive. We should always seek for the best boyfriend.
You should be careful, it's not rare to find
a girl who work for her boyfriend to school and then be abandoned.
I won't be with him for 7 years if he were that kind of boy.
Is everything ok with your boyfriend?
Just worry about yourself.
You've been together for 7 years.
Even if you were as pretty as me, men would still be bored with you.
Men are always looking for new targets.
Look, you can't even call him when you need him.
I can, but I don't want to.
Really?
Ji Hee! Seo Ji Hee!
Seo Ji Hee!
Darling.
Wake up.
Ji Hee!
I am so sleepy.
So sleepy.
Wake up! Let's go.
Five more minutes.
Wake up! Be quick.
I'm so tired.
Get up and have the breakfast. Come on.
Why do you get up so early?
Sit.
I'm so sleepy.
I don't want to take the breakfast.
It's aromatic.
That's why I like to be here.
Water, Water.
Water.
Give me some water.
You did it on purpose. Come over here.
You did it on purporse, right? My mouth is burning.
I want to make your heart burning.
You always come to me late at night, I hate you.
It's so spicy!
Give me some water.
Water.
I should stop hating you and love you again.
Min Hyuk!
Your father is looking for you.
- If he knew you were here. - Have you found her?
She has left Daejeon.
Now we are looking for her in Suwon.
Sorry.
Don't say sorry. Go find her.
Get out.
I am
a prosecutor who help people in need.
I only strive to find the truth and justice.
I swear to be an upright presecutor.
Where have you been?
Where is father?
- What? - Is he out?
I don't know.
What a brat! Go to school.
Who do you think you are!
8.74 million KRW.
These are the fines issued to your car last month.
24.5 million KRW, for hotel room charges,
and the clothes that you bought for your lady friends.
You don't have moeny to buy your own underwear.
I have raised you to this age, even if you can't help me to run the company,
you should at least not embarrass me.
Tell your brother to come back to Seoul.
The resort in Cheongju is running well now.
He'll be in charge of the hotel.
You can take charge of the casino and the theater.
Darling. - Father.
Apologize to Congressman Shin, and cancel the engagement.
It's my fault to spoil him.
Get out. I have nothing to say to you.
Darling.
Min Hyuk has already bought an engagement ring for Se Yeon.
He must feel awkward to be engaged with his friend at first.
Se Yeon is arriving today, right?
I told Congressman Shin that we'd go pick her up at the airport.
Are you going to pick her up?
Of course. I should go pick up Se Yeon.
Forgive him.
He's still young.
He'll grow up when he gets married.
I'm aware of that.
Min Hyuk.
Are you going to the airport?
You should take the ring.
I can tolerate you act like that when my father is around,
but don't smile and speak like that when no one is here.
It makes me feel sick.
Min Hyuk, don't you know how to say thank you?
Good-bye.
OK.
Thanks. Here's your receipt and 2400KRW.
Drive safely.
Hello.
Thank you.
Put that in the garbage.
- OK. Here you are. - Thanks.
Drive safely.
Look how greedy you eat.
Don't eat so fast.
Drive safely.
It’s too much for you to eat. I'll help you to finish it.
Don't be so stingy.
Rich people spend money like nothing.
I suffered a lot, but still have no money.
Don't be kidding. You’ve spent all your money on making up and buying clothes.
Do you call that suffer?
- Look at Yoo Jung. She works day and night. - Yes.
For her dear boyfriend.
She's penniless aftre working for 10 years.
Yesterday, she...
Isn't it delicious?
Where are we having dinner tonight? Potato soup again?
I don’t know.
I can’t go anyway.
Why?
It's an important day.
Haven't seen you for a long time, Se Yeon.
What are you doing here?
What can I do at the airport except for picking you up?
This is for you, the ring.
We’ve been friends since we were kids.
How can we be married?
Don't wanna take it?
Don't marry me if you don't want to.
Don’t use your father as an excuse.
I never said I didn’t want to marry you.
Why wouldn’t I like it?
The presecutors always investigate us due to the petty cash.
If I married you, your father will help us out.
We can sponsor your father financially.
This is a win-win situation.
We're marrying for the benefit of our families.
It's better to marry you than a total stranger.
Is that all?
What else? Just take it.
It's very expensive.
No doubt. All you have is money.
Then why not accept it?
I'll throw it away.
Is it that cheap in your eyes?
Then throw it away.
What should we do?
Just tell your father that you don’t want to marry me.
What if I do?
I'll do whatever you want.
I can’t tell my father.
If I told him that I won't marry you,
he'll beat me to death.
Your father doesn’t like me, either.
Even if you are a rogue, it doesn’t matter to him.
He needs your father's money.
What a bad day!
You don’t want to live with me, right?
Can you imagine us sleeping together?
You smiled.
You will break off the engagement, right?
Hello. I'm Number 8 staff.
Hey, you work here.
The toll is 8000KRW.
I didn’t bring my wallet.
I'll send the bill to your company,
or you can go to the office over there.
Thanks to you, I dind't drive after drinking.
Thank you.
I'll send the bill to your address.
You still owe me 15000KRW for last night.
You are asking me to pay for you?
You'll be rich one day.
But, I don’t have any money.
Can you lend me some?
What?
How much?
Don't bother. I'll pay her.
I don’t like being in debt.
Hold this as collateral.
What are you doing?
Since you didn't want it.
Take this as collateral.
Sir!
The customer is always right, right?
You should listen to the customer.
Take it.
Nice catch.
Hey!
Min Hyuk!
Take care of it. I'll come back for it.
You not only don't respect money,
but also have no respect for other.
You're right.
Stop tapping my window.
See you later.
Hey, hey...
Stop!
Sorry.
Sorry, sir.
I'm sorry. OK.
What do you want to do?
You don’t want the ring,
but you don’t want anyone else to have it?
Do you think I'll care about that ring?
You used the ring to embarrass me in front of that kind of girl.
That's Se Yeon.
Sorry.
Yoo Jung, are those real diamonds?
Can I try it on?
It doesn't belong to us.
I may never have the chance to wear a ring like this.
Let me put it on just once.
- No. - Just once.
Please.
You baked a cake for your anniversary.
Why not give him a gift certificate or a smart phone?
There’s nothing special about that.
This is different.
You're paying too much.
Did he call you even once today?
See! He didn’t call you.
Why do you bother taking this to him?
Let's just eat it here.
Hey! Hae Ri!
Before I hurt you, hand that box to me.
Sorry, here you are.
You'd better pray for it to be intact.
Hello. I’m Ahn Do Hoon.
You’re quite handsome for a prosecutor.
You can leave a voice mail.
Hello, Do Hoon. Have you been busy?
It’s okay. What time should we meet each other?
Okay.
How come she's not calling me?
What a torture.
What did they say?
I'm sure they liked Do Hoon.
- What? - Yes.
Enough.
Of course. Why bother saying so much.
Don't worry about it.
- Do Hoon is smart. - Who is that?
-Passing the bar exam was a piece of cake for him. - Hello, you're home.
Yoo Jung!
- Others can't compare with him - Why do you bring so many things?
- Come in. It must be heavy. - Yes.
Mother, how are you?
Right.
Madam Park, let me know when you find out.
What are you doing here? Do Hoon will come home late today.
I come here to see you two.
The pumpkin is very sweet.
This is entrepreneur.
You don’t have to do that. Do Hoon will eat out tonight.
Father coughs a lot recently.
We can steam it as a snack.
This can cure constipation. You should try some.
You don’t have to do this. No one will eat it.
It's almost done. Don't worry and have a rest.
I can't rest when an outsider is working in my kitchen.
How can I be an outsider?
Don't you regard me as your daughter?
I still feel uncomfortable.
It's almost done. I'll be finished soon.
So talktive.
How can you be so clumsy?
Look what you did.
Is it so hard to peel some garlic?
- That's why our life is so miserable. - Mom. You have a phone call.
Don't nag me.
- Ah. - Hello.
Hey, the girl's side seem to like Do Hoon.
What did Do Hoon say? They're willing to arrange an office to Do Hoon.
Hold on, I'll give the phone to her.
Mother, it's for you.
Is garlic more important than me?
Yes, garlic is more important than you.
- I'm your husband! - Hello.
Oh.
I'll call you later.
How can I be so sleepy.
Yoo Jung, that's enough.
Sour apples make us burp all night.
Okay.
What a pity！
You couldn't see Do Hoon today.
It's okay. I came here to see you.
I'll leave now. Have a good rest.
Are you leaving?
Don't come too often.
It's not good for your reputation.
I'll leave now.
OK.
Take care.
You can't make use of our son.
What are you talking about?
She has to handel everything herself,
since her mother passed away when she was young.
Delicious.
Okay.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Take care.
Who is that?
I want to expand the shop to the warehouse,
and renovate it.
Renovate?
You always say that you don't have any money.
Where is the money from?
I'm not asking for your money.
You're marrying a prosecutor.
We should at least have a decent house.
I'm not marrying a prosecutor. I'm marrying Do Hoon.
I heard that a girl needs 3 keys,
to marry a prosecutor.
I have no money.
I have a beautiful face.
I have a nice figure.
And I have a kind heart.
I think these three can equal to the three keys.
I saved you a lot of money.
Stop being silly.
Don't drink that.
Drink those after the expiration date.
Dad. How can you have the heart to let me drink it?
Why are you yelling at me?
It's still okay to drink.
I won't drink it.
I won't drink it. Drink it yourself.
What's wrong with her?
Yoo Jung!
What is it?
Did Do Hoon give that to you?
Why didn't you tell me just now?
Have you decided on the date?
We haven't discussed anything specific yet.
Do Hoon is here.
Come on out.
Where are we going?
It's not convenient here. Get in the car, please.
Why?
Just tell me directly what you want to say.
Don't bring me to somewhere strange.
Get in the car, please.
How long should I wait?
I have a lesson soon.
Min Joo!
Sorry.
My father's running late because of his party meeting.
You don't have to be sorry.
Mr. Park is here.
See? My tutor is here.
Thanks to you, I couldn't have dinner.
Steward, prepare some snacks for her.
Okay.
I'll arrange another date.
You'll become our family member soon.
We'll have plenty of time to eat together.
Sir, my father has an election in his district in October.
How about announcing our marriage before that?
Sounds good to me.
Have some more.
That's okay.
Why is it so hard to eat with family?
Madam, there's no family here.
The soup is too salty.
Is it?
Mr. Yun, she said the soup is salty.
How come you can't satisfy my fiancee?
Sorry, miss.
I'll make a new one.
It's okay, Mr. Yun.
We have plenty of time to work on it.
Se Yeon!
I'm your future wife.
You should call me more gently.
Do you remember here?
When we first came here,
you were working outside all day long, and your face was tanned.
So you didn't want to take a picture.
That was taken on our first date.
We were wearing matching shirts.
And that one is
when I passed my bar exa,
you were drunk and singing, I took it secretly.
Although that's good, don't do it again.
What do you want to say?
Yoo Jung, I'm sorry that I went on a blind date.
And it's my fault not telling you the truth.
I'll never do it again.
It's just a stupid thing my mother arranged.
Do you know what day it is today?
We've been dating for seven years.
But for you,
I could not make such an accomplishment.
The things you have done for me,
I'll never forget till death.
No, I'll never forget even after my death.
Yoo Jung.
Will you marry me?
I'm a mess, aren't I?
You are, but you're still pretty.
Do you like me?
Huh? I know you don't.
Why do you want to marry me?
I'll do whatever you want.
Really? What I want is you.
What's wrong with you?
The soup was that salty?
I don't care who I marry.
I'm going to end up with someone that my father finds for me.
You are no different than me.
What you said is right.
I'd rather marry someone I knew than a total stranger.
Don't push yourself too hard.
We're no match for our parents.
You even broke up with Seo Ji Hee, the love of your life.
Even if you get married,
how long do you think you two would've survived without money?
I haven't broken up with her. Don't talk nonsense.
Are you going to marry her, then?
Then go. Tell your father what you want.
You can't do it.
You thought you'd die without her.
Yet, you've lived for 6 months without her.
However, without your father's money,
you wouldn't survive a day.
Just accept the reality.
Do you think your father will spoil you forever?
You suck.
Yoo Jung, I love you. We'll be happy together.
Let me take a picture of you two.
One, two, three.
Congratulations!
Father, I have something to tell you.
Shin Sang Hoon! That bastard!
How dare he stood me up!
He's well known for treating those who are lower than him badly.
Lower than him?
Listen to me carefully!
I need his reputation at the moment,
but he'll be begging for my help soon.
Money talks!
You're right.
This marriage isn't for your happiness.
The rumor of us becoming Congressman Shin's in-laws
have already increased the value of our stock.
Name the day quickly.
Can I divorce after the marriage?
You must be crazy.
Who is that? Ji Hee?
Is that you? Ji Hee, answer me.
Ji Hee! I know it's you.
Ji Hee, where are you?
Jo Min Hyuk!
Pull yourself together.
Hello, where is this?
This is Art Cafe.
Why isn't it working?
- It's not? - That's strange.
- Wait a moment. - OK.
Yes, I'm almost there.
What should we do?
What the...
Let's go!
It's not easy to drive it in the rain.
- Thank you. - What?
For marrying me.
Don't say that. It's you who marry me.
I love you.
Stop staring at me.
Yoo Jung, are you okay?
Yes.
What did we hit?
I don't know.
It's too dangerous. You stay here.
I'll see what happened.
Do Hoon.
Listen to me. It's okay.
Do Hoon! Do Hoon!
I told you to stay inside.
What was it?
Thank god.
- Let's get out of here. - Wait.
Let's move it. Other cars might hit it.
Should we call the insurance company?
No.
I think we should.
It's okay.
I had two glasses of wine earlier.
I don't want to make things complicated.
That seems to be an abandoned car.
Yes.
I think this is a good sign.
When the car lost control, I thought we'd die.
Yet, we're safe and sound.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I think we'll live happily ever after.
Sure we will.
Right.
Have you found her?
Where are you?
Do Hoon, your bumper's damaged. The windshield wipers are broken as well.
Let's drive it to a garage.
It'll cost a lot to fix it. The car is too old.
I can buy a new one.
No, we can get a few more years out of it.
Leave it here. I'll fix it.
I'll take care of it. Get inside.
Okay.
Drive carefully.
Dad.
What?
He proposed to me.
You already told me.
I forgot. I just want to tell you again.
What's wrong with your forehead? Are you hurt?
I just bumped it.
Let me see. It's swollen.
Wait. I'll get some ice.
I said I'm okay.
Have a good sleep.
Ji Hee! Ji Hee!
You can't come in.
Ji Hee! What happened?
Ji Hee! Ji Hee!
Kwang Soo, what happened?
I think it was a hit-and-run.
Ji Hee! Seo Ji Hee!
Ji Hee! Ji Hee! Wake up.
Ji Hee. Ji Hee!
Ji Hee!
I said I'd follow you to the end of the world.
I said wherever you hid, I'd find you.
I told you not to die without my permission.
Don't die!
Sorry, wait a moment.
Come on!
Next on secret love.
- I found it. - Who is she?
We have evidence.
How dare you hurt my woman?
I said I was driving.
Please help my boyfriend.
Here is your case. Her name is Kang Yoo Jung.
Make her suffer.
I'll drive.
I'm worried about you.
Do you know why you were arrested?
Hey! Hit-and run!